<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Milind/Sonavane]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Milind/Sonavane]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/milindsonavane/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2016 00:52:21 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/milindsonavane/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Designer, Technologist, Entrepreneur, Maker, Artist... Fusionist from India.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Designer, Technologist, Entrepreneur, Maker, Artist... Fusionist from India.</h1><p>Every subsequent stage of my life has given me skills, ideas and experiences that, logically and emotionally, now point towards New Media Design as the basis for the work of my life. 
</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/milindsonavane/58a5e78d-9bf4-4405-9f69-b234904d42d3/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">58a5e78d-9bf4-4405-9f69-b234904d42d3</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 23:51:24 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rural Roots, Connected Learning]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Rural Roots, Connected Learning</h1><p>I was born and brought up in Chindavali, a small village of about 800 
people on the banks of the Krishna river, about 120 kilometres away from
 the then expanding urban sprawl of Pune. My parents were both teachers 
by profession. My mother in particular was responsible for the inception
 of visual communication in my mind, many years before I came across the
 term in the modern world. Her teaching methods were unconventional, and
 involved the use of ever new ‘educational toys’ crafted from scrap to 
make sure her students got the point, again well before similar ‘modern’
 teaching methods were introduced in urban Indian schools a good twenty 
years later. </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/milindsonavane/rural-roots-connected-learning/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3519eb51-bba0-4ec1-b789-73e6d9200abc</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 23:57:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/96ed9ed4-58cc-4969-84b5-26c8d0f8dce9.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/milindsonavane/324f11d1-ae57-4e0e-bbe7-d776f91f1060/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">324f11d1-ae57-4e0e-bbe7-d776f91f1060</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 23:36:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artistic Development]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Artistic Development</h1><p>My secondary education took place in a slightly larger public 
residential school, which was run much in the manner of a military 
school in terms of organization and discipline. However, it also had a 
focused and efficient art division, headed by one extremely creative 
teacher who would make his own shoes, literally, and organize 
competitions for making clay Ganesha idols for annual festivities. This 
was also the time when I got involved seriously with art, giving my 
initial state-sponsored exams that would lead me to graduate in applied 
arts.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/a2049e8ccf8ff44ff79a480949fdec1e25d36dd1.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/milindsonavane/artistic-development/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f0806a76-74c1-42b9-98e5-aa783e4033aa</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2016 00:39:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Professional Endeavours]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Professional Endeavours</h1><p>I felt the impact of a globalized India like never before as soon as I 
stepped into the professional world. If my formative years had given me 
the roots, my professional career gave me the leaves that could breathe 
in the air from around the world. Commercial vocation took me into the 
booming field of Information Technology, where I joined the digital 
industry and worked in different capacities – from employee to 
entrepreneur – as a User Interface – User Experience professional. 
Coming from an arts background had its uses, but the exposure received 
in the digital domain – phone apps, gaming and software 
applications – brought me up to speed with where the world was, and 
where it was headed. It is very important for me personally to stay 
connected with the world in this way, through my work.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/b6efb9a6-6079-4290-9f0c-24ed8a5f5f74.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/milindsonavane/professional-endeavours/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c2692383-cb62-4169-8764-19ee9dde431a</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2016 00:51:24 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Way Ahead]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The Way Ahead</h1><p>After serving in the corporate world in different capacities for over ten years, doing work that I am proud of and gaining critical skills, I have recently begun my own endeavours into making activities, and trying to ensure that the consumerist scenario does not take away the joys of making by passing it on to the next generation. Makerspark, an initiative I have recently started, is working in this direction. (www.makerspark.in). In my view, this is the culmination of everything I have done in the past – being connected to teaching, a community-based way of working, learning through skill exchange, art and expression, solving problems through design, and work in the electronic and digital domains. I intend to take this work into my future.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/milindsonavane/the-way-ahead/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">57070aba-862d-4f78-b886-4fa735874495</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 23:18:18 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RudeFood]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>RudeFood</h1><p>littleBits got its global chapters to get together and make things on March 28, 2015. We made music, chopped veggies and spun them around. Watch!</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/993252dc354e04a1efa391d9649a2b9253fd1e61.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://vimeo.com/124199065</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ed74a496-f075-454f-9e5e-51d00035f3a6</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 23:12:17 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[YoungMinds]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>YoungMinds</h1><p>Give a child something interesting to do. Watch. Learn. Make it even more interesting the next time. That's the Spark in Makerspark.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/5a02117cd85672c6d285890921b9868ebb27d76c.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/milindsonavane/youngminds/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">fbde6e81-fc7f-41c5-ad3f-5390c8a5dc4c</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 23:12:17 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ButterBot]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>ButterBot</h1><p>Coffee in the morning? Nah. We have buttermilk. Powered by littleBits. Made the Indian way.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/3d4a8b4206a7a69fcddf8094a1eebd4a5172eea5.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://vimeo.com/115063814</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">793ee3d4-7482-46cf-b9a4-02ce7d2e12eb</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 23:12:17 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>milind.sonavane@gmail.com</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/milindsonavane/84fe873a-7a77-4ea6-885b-32f990d87ece/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">84fe873a-7a77-4ea6-885b-32f990d87ece</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 23:10:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>