<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Milind/Sonavane]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Milind/Sonavane]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/milindsonavane/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 20:31:54 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/milindsonavane/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Designer, Technologist, Entrepreneur, Maker, Artist... Fusionist from India.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Designer, Technologist, Entrepreneur, Maker, Artist... Fusionist from India.</h1><p>Every subsequent stage of my life has given me skills, ideas and experiences that, logically and emotionally, now point towards New Media Design as the basis for the work of my life. </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/milindsonavane/5b231be8-89dd-4b45-b675-59450e10d7da/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5b231be8-89dd-4b45-b675-59450e10d7da</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 20:28:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rural Roots, Connected Learning]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Rural Roots, Connected Learning</h1><p>I was brought up in Chindavali, a small village of about 800 people on the banks of the Krishna river, about 120 kilometers away from the then expanding urban sprawl of Pune. My parents were both teachers by profession. My mother in particular was responsible for the inception of visual communication in my mind, many years before I came across the term in the modern world. Her teaching methods were unconventional, and involved the use of ever new ‘educational toys’ crafted from scrap to make sure her students got the point, again well before similar ‘modern’ teaching methods were introduced in urban Indian schools a good twenty years later. </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/milindsonavane/rural-roots-connected-learning/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">cf9ae233-1843-471a-84b8-e7db6473e758</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 19:42:31 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Professional Endeavours]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Professional Endeavours</h1><p>I felt the impact of a globalized India like never before as soon as I stepped into the professional world. If my formative years had given me the roots, my professional career gave me the leaves that could breathe in the air from around the world. Commercial vocation took me into the booming field of Information Technology, where I joined the digital industry and worked in different capacities – from employee to entrepreneur – as a User Interface – User Experience professional. Coming from an arts background had its uses, but the exposure received in the digital domain – websites, phone apps, gaming and other applications – brought me up to speed with where the world was, and where it was headed. It is very important for me personally to stay connected with the world in this way, through my work.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/milindsonavane/professional-endeavours/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">84f888fa-59e4-4e9e-987a-7cfb7a6e4e5c</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 19:39:29 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Way Ahead ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The Way Ahead </h1><p>After serving in the corporate world in different capacities for over ten years, doing work that I am proud of and gaining critical skills, I have recently begun my own endeavours into making activities, and trying to ensure that the consumerist scenario does not take away the joys of making by passing it on to the next generation. Makerspark, an initiative I have recently started, is working in this direction. (www.makerspark.in). In my view, this is the culmination of everything I have done in the past – being connected to teaching, a community-based way of working, learning through skill exchange, art and expression, solving problems through design, and work in the electronic and digital domains. My past enables me to understand and work effectively in this field, and I intend to take this work into my future…</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/milindsonavane/the-way-ahead/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">aa85c4b6-dc41-4f96-b0e9-1f0ec3986d9e</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 19:38:04 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>